{
    "id": "53757799ea524e73b6c95c0f89d60f31",
    "title": "So, To And For",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Susie talked to the shy girl ………………………. she wouldn’t feel left out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "so that"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5adea491954849728fe795d99634c87d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am going …………………… ask her out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d5212c3f81004e33abd2fc28fc747c87"
        },
        {
            "question": "They aren’t going ……………………… come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "361155071640484a92c8f1580d69d2b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s have a break ………………… lunch.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "so that",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0c3952930c7a4cd8ac493b06452cf274"
        },
        {
            "question": "The weather is stormy and will remain …………………. over the weekend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "so",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d0311b0c77774e75b7b700fadff77e03"
        },
        {
            "question": "I offer you new lamps ………………… old.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "so that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "39042478bceb40efb0e3ac949ae4b400"
        },
        {
            "question": "We could not see ……………………… smoke.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "962ca835b06e4d86b523ccf76cb87be9"
        },
        {
            "question": "She went ………………………. the market.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3e358dd6cad64951960744a1eb4efd71"
        },
        {
            "question": "She prefers dogs ………………….. cats.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cad3c85fd0d14ff18403f14ba288f96b"
        },
        {
            "question": "They got …………………… their destination.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b79aa78b6b274117b5f3239aa5d6f53c"
        }
    ]
}